http://www.americansurplus.com/privacy-policy/

Used Equipment Used BalersUsed Bins and Used Totes Used Storage BinsUsed Louvered PanelsUsed Finger Lid TotesUsed IBC TotesUsed Plastic TotesUsed Corrugated BinsUsed Stackable BinsUsed Nestable TotesUsed Divider BoxesUsed Cantilever RackUsed Conveyor Used Gravity ConveyorUsed Power Conveyor Used Conveyor AccessoriesUsed Conveyor Systems Used Dock Equipment Used Dock Levelers Used Yard Ramp Used High Speed DoorsUsed Rail Dock BoardsUsed Edge Of Dock LevelersUsed Dock Plates Used Dock Boards Used Air CurtainsUsed Scissor DocksUsed Floor ScrubbersUsed Flow Rack Used Carton Flow Rack Used Pallet Flow Rack Used Span Track Used Skatewheel Flow Rack Used Mobile Gravity Flow Rack Used Pallet Flow RailsUsed Forklifts Used Reach TrucksUsed Propane Forklifts Used Electric ForkliftsUsed Manual Pallet Jacks Used Electric Pallet Jacks Used Order Pickers Used Narrow Aisle Forklifts Used Turret Trucks Used Stacker Used Forklift Battery Charger Used Forklift Battery Handling Equipment Used Forklift Attachments Used Horizontal CarouselsUsed Hoppers Used Tilt TrucksUsed Plastic Utility HoppersUsed Inplant OfficesUsed Industrial Cabinets Used Flammable Storage Cabinet Used Vidmar CabinetUsed Blueprint Cabinet Used Industrial Containers Used Wire BasketsUsed IBC TotesUsed Bulk Containers Used Industrial Hampers Used Lift Equipment Used Gantry CranesUsed Jib CranesUsed Bridge CranesUsed Chain HoistsUsed Lift Tables Used Pallet Positioner Used Vertical Lift Used Lockers Used Full Door Lockers Used Box Lockers Used Half Door Lockers Used Garment Lockers Used Mezzanines Used Steel MezzaninesUsed Pallet Rack MezzaninesUsed Shelf Supported MezzaninesUsed Mezzanine Flooring Used Mezzanine Catwalks Used Mezzanine GatesUsed Mezzanine StairwaysUsed Vertical Lift Used Packaging Equipment Used Case ErectorsUsed Case Sealers Used Stretch WrappersUsed Heat TunnelsUsed Strapping Machines Used Automatic Tape DispensersUsed Industrial Label PrintersUsed Pallet Rack Decking Used Wire DeckingUsed Wire DeckingUsed Open Rack DeckingUsed Open Rack DeckingUsed Pallet Racking Used Teardrop Pallet Racking Used Structural Pallet Racking Used Selective Pallet RackingUsed Drive In RacksUsed Pushback Racking Used Pallet Flow Rack Used Pallet Rack Accessories Used Pallet Rack Supports Used Pallet Rack DeckingUsed Pick Modules Used Rolling LaddersUsed Safety Products Used Warehouse Guard Rail Used Column Protectors Used Dome MirrorsUsed Folding Security Gates Used Anti Fatigue MatsUsed Drum Handling Equipment Used Scales Used Conveyor ScalesUsed Counting ScalesUsed Floor ScalesUsed Dimensioning SystemsUsed Shelving Used Steel Shelving Used Industrial Shelving Used Warehouse Shelving Used Rivet Rack Shelving Used Shelf Supported MezzaninesUsed Wire ShelvingUsed Record Storage Shelving Used Modular Drawer Shelving Used Storage Racks Used Stack Racks Used Bulk RackUsed Carpet Rack Used Reel Rack Used Warehouse Carts Used Utility Carts Used Platform TrucksUsed Rolling Z-Racks Used Shelf Stock TrucksUsed Bin CartsUsed Ladder CartsUsed Basket CartsUsed Steel Tray CartsUsed Tote Carts Used Wire CartsUsed Casters Used Warehouse Fans Used Industrial Barrel Fans Used Air CannonsUsed Pedestal Fans Used Wall Mounted FansUsed Wire Security CagesUsed Workbenches Used Pallet Rack Workbenches Used Laboratory BenchesUsed Butcher Block WorkbenchesUsed Packing TablesUsed Shop DesksUsed Utility VehiclesLatest LiquidationsNew Equipment Teardrop Pallet RacksCantilever RacksInplant OfficesWire DecksWire BasketsStack RacksStretch WrappersYard RampsScalesSelf Dumping HoppersRolling LaddersFlammable CabinetsDock BoardsDock PlatesPedestal FansRack Protectionother-equipment SecretBargains
About ASI
Our Facility
Services
Financing
Installation
Custom Fabrication
Layout Design / CAD Drawings
Liquidations
Privacy Policy
Collection of your Personal InformationAmerican Surplus automatically tracks the domain from which you accessed our website and the pages you accessed. We use this data to analyze trends and statistics to help better understand how our website is utilized. We also collect information provided by visitors via online forms, registration forms and surveys.Use of Personal Data CollectedAmerican Surplus collects and uses your personal information to operate the American Surplus website and deliver the services you have requested. American Surplus also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from American Surplus. American Surplus may also contact you to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new products or services.American Surplus does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. However, American Surplus may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to American Surplus, and they are required to maintain the confidentially of your information.We keep track of the websites and pages our customers visit within American Surplus to determine which services are most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.American Surplus websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on American Surplus or the site; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of American Surplus; and (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of American Surplus, or the public.American Surplus does not attempt to collect personal information from visitors under 13 years of age. Personal information sent to American Surplus, such as e-mail, which appears to be from a child, is deleted. American Surplus cannot always determine if a visitor to our website or sender of an e-mail is under 13. American Surplus links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy of such other sites. American Surplus does not review or control such sites and suggests that you review the privacy of such sites.Use of CookiesAmerican Surplus's website uses cookies to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize American Surplus pages, or register with American Surplus site or services, a cookie helps America Surplus to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same American Surplus website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the American Surplus features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the American Surplus services or websites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationAmerican Surplus secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. American Surplus secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.McAfee Security SealThe information you submit through forms that are not guaranteed secure potentially run the risk of having this data compromised. To ensure our security, American Surplus joins with McAfee SECURE security to submit information to our site.The McAfee SECURE Symbol displays ensuring customers the site has passed their daily security tests. This protects visitors from identity theft, viruses, spyware, and other online threats.The McAfee SECURE Trustmark only appears when American Surplus has passed McAfee intensive, daily security scan. Tests include personal information access, links to dangerous sites, phishing, and other online dangers.Changes to this StatementAmerican Surplus will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. American Surplus encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how American Surplus is protecting your information.
